# Micah Ellis

### **SKILLS**

Citrix Counterpoint ADP & SAP Microsoft Office JavaScript CSS HTML Python MongoDB PostgreSQL Mongoose **JQuery** Github Node React Django Bootstrap Express

#### **ACHIEVEMENTS**

Built and deployed employee scheduling template using Excel based on payroll dollars to all locations.

Won 7 Platinum Performer awards for revenue and contribution growth.

Strategically reduced store expenditures by lowering the cost of supplies and lowering on the job injuries.

Achieved record sales at various locations for multiple months throughout career.

Maintained culture of safety in warehouse environment achieving 1-year accident-free.

#### **EXPERIENCE**

#### **General Assembly, Remote** — Student

July 2020 - October 2020

• Three-month, 500-hour full-time and full-stack program conducted in a remote setting, providing experience with the latest front- and back-end programming languages, tools, and methodologies.

## Goodwill Industries, Denver, CO & Atlanta, GA - Store Manager

October 2013 - July 2020

- Manage a team of 60+ employees with diverse individual needs.
- Responsible for store scheduling and daily operations.
- Oversee employee training, development, & leadership.
- Recruit, interview, and hire direct reports.

- Resolve customer complaints.
- Review operational records and reports to project sales and determine profitability.

## Target Corporation, Atlanta, GA - Executive Team Lead

September 2004 - October 2013

- Consistently exceeded company goals for completion times.
- Ensure planogram goals are met while minimizing the impact on customer shopping habits.
- Direct and coordinate all activities involving pricing and planograms.

## **EDUCATION**

**General Assembly, Remote** — Software Engineering Immersive 2020

Auburn University of Montgomery, Alabama — Information Technology 2004 - 2007